Patrick M. Kelliher

rehillek76@gmail.com | 415.225.8916 | San Francisco Bay Area

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Extensive hardware and software installation, integration, and maintenance knowledge with a proven track record providing technical support expertise to numerous Bay Area companies. Excellent communication and people skills established through my years of delighting customers and working in team environments to resolve complex technical issues. A self-starter that is well organized and capable of multitasking with numerous responsibilities while meeting tight deadlines.

TECHNOLOGICAL INVENTORY

Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows, Sun/Oracle Solaris, Red Hat, and Ubuntu, macOS

Languages: JavaScript (ES5, ES6), HTML5, CSS3, SQL, Linux Bash scripting. (working knowledge): Ruby **Technologies:** Node.js, Express, MongoDB, React.js, Reactstrap, Redux, REST API, Django, Django REST Framework, MySQL, Sequelize.js, Mocha.js unit testing, Handlebars.js, Firebase, jQuery, JSON, AJAX, Bootstrap, Materialize, Material-UI, Git, Heroku, Travis CI

Software/SaaS/LaaS: VMWare, MS Office, G Suite, Adobe (Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat), TweetDeck, PayPal, Stripe, MS SharePoint DMS, Putty, Tableau, MailChimp, Slack, Splunk, PagerDuty, GitHub, AWS,

GCP, Google BigQuery, Imgix, Jenkins

CRM: Salesforce, Zendesk, Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

Greenhouse Software (Current) - Support Engineer II

Imgix, San Francisco, CA Jan 2019 to May 2019 - Support Engineer

Fielded incoming Zendesk support tickets, resolving technical questions, software functionality, configuration, service incidents, and other variable conflict issues associated with the Imgix image processing API. Advocated for customers in escalating product enhancement and API-related issues to the engineering team, internally taking end-to-end ownership, and keeping customers apprised throughout the support lifecycle.

- Reduced support ticket time to resolution from 72 to 24 hours aligning support with sales to
 exceed expected customer service level agreements and roughly a 10% increase in customer
 satisfaction scores.
- Lessened the impact on engineering team resources by diagnosing irregularities and changes with the Imgix API documentation and editing the associated HTML and Markdown files on the Imgix front-end website.

Opus 2 International, San Francisco, CA June 2016 to March 2018 - Application Support Specialist Served as a technical resource and escalation point for the tier 1 support, product marketing, and sales teams spearheaded internal training on technical and product-related issues, evaluating back-end, network, and server related issues via the Linux command line editing Apache, Nginx, Tomcat, PHP, and Docker config files, grepping and sorting associated log files for the entire Opus 2 trial preparation and case management software

suite.

- Promoted revenue preservation (contract renewals) through client-facing, technical escalation solution development. Replicated these solutions, scaling them for company-wide deployment.
- Reduced software rollout redundancy by implemented a quality assurance peer-review procedure to test new features and bug fixes for each software revision update.

Microsoft (Contract), San Francisco, CA Feb 2016 to June 2016 - Technical Support Engineer

Triaged customer-facing MileIQ mileage tracking mobile application and web-related support inquiries via Zendesk and coordinated with engineering via Jira.

- Facilitated a more unified and cohesive support experience resulting in an increase in customer satisfaction scores, establishing support protocols utilizing Zendesk macros to accelerate tier support representative response times by 15%.
- Fostered a more collaborative partnership between the support and engineering teams to address customer product enhancement requests, bug-related issues as well as track device, mobile iOS, and Android-related issues keeping MileIQ customers' needs in constant focus.

Zillow San Francisco, CA June 2014 to Aug 2015 - Technical Feed Operations

Diagnosed and verified partner submitted JSON and XML feeds and chartered the real-time feed campaign for rental listings on the HotPads, Zillow, and Trulia rental and housing listing networks.

- Developed and managed relationships with key partners and administrators to ensure the early adoption and usage of Zillow network services, coordinating with the fraud and engineering teams to enrich partners listing quality into compliance.
- Resolved a critical JSON feed issue from a recent acquisition (Trulia), leading to a 100% correction in data flow. This fix improved over 500 partner feeds, significantly improving the Brokerage user experience while contributing to channel revenues.

Tracker Corporation, San Francisco, CA Oct 2013 to May 2014 - QA

Workshare, San Francisco, CA May 2009 to Nov 2011 - Technical Support Engineer

PayPal, San Jose, CA Nov 1999 to Sept 2007 - Technical Support Engineer

CATS (Computer Assisted Testing Service), Burlingame, CA Jan 1999 to Nov 1999 - Network Helpdesk / Desktop Support

EDUCATION

UC Berkeley, Full Stack Web Development Certificate CCSF, San Francisco, CA - Economics AA College of San Mateo, CA - Economics AA GE Access - Sun Solaris
Certificate Microsoft - Certified MS Professional